George Salter Papers, 1920-1980
Mortimer Rare Book Room, William Allan Neilson Library, Smith College
Jefferson Selleck Jonas, Carl Little Brown and Co. 1951 2:66
John Bull zu Hause Silex, Karl E.A. Seemann Verlag n.d. 3:88
Jonathan Found Maiden, Cecil Crowell Publishers n.d. 1:16
Joseph and His Brothers Mann, Thomas Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 1:49
Journey From the East Gayn, Mark J. Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 1:49
Journey of Tapiola Nathan, Robert Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:50
Journey of Tapiola Nathan, Robert Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:53
Journey of Tapiola Nathan, Robert Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:62
Judgment of Paris, The Vidal, Gore Dutton n.d. 1:20
Jugend in Sowjet-Russland, Die Mehnert, Klaus S. Fisher Verlag n.d. 1:25
Juggernaut Over Holland van Kleffens, E.N. Columbia University Press n.d. 1:13
Junggesellin, Die Margueritte, Victor Erich Reiss Verlag n.d. 3:86
Jungle Deutsche Lyrik Heuschele, Otto Philipp Reclam Verlag n.d. 3:84
Kapital, Das Marx, Karl Kiepenheuer n.d. 1:46
Kautschukzapfer de Castro, Ferreira Gebruder Enoch n.d. 1:31
Kingdom of Innocents Cram, Mildred Knopf, Alfred A. 1940 1:52
Knaben und Manner Zweig, Arnold Kiepenheuer n.d. 1:46
Konig Alkohol London, Jack Universitas, Berlin n.d. 3:99
Lambs, The Anthony, Katharine Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:50
Lament Lloyd, A. L. Oxford University Press 1937 2:74
Lamp Post, The Gregor-Dellin, Martin Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:58
Land I Live, The Longstreet, Stephen Random House 1942 2:80
Leben Eines Propheten, Das Mohammed Kiepenheuer n.d. 1:44
Leben Stanleys von Jakob Wasserman, Das Matari, Bula S. Fisher Verlag n.d. 1:27
Letters of Ralph Waldo Emerson, The Rusk, Ralph L. (ed.) Columbia University Press n.d. 1:13
Letzte Gott, Der Farrere, Claude Kiepenheuer n.d. 1:45
Letzten Segelschiffe, die Hauser, Heinrich S. Fisher Verlag n.d. 1:26
Life and Death of a Spanish Town, The Paul, Elliot Random House 1937 2:80
Life at the Top Braine, John Houghton Mifflin Co. 1962 1:42
Light of Day, The Ambler, Eric Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:55
Living Thoughts of Darwin, The Huxley, Julian Longman's 1939 2:68
Living Thoughts of Mazzini, The Silone, Ignazio Longman's n.d. 2:68
Living Thoughts of Montaigne, The Gide, Andre Longman's n.d. 2:68
Living Thoughts of Nietzsche, The Mann, Heinrich Longman's n.d. 2:68
Living Thoughts of Rousseau, The Rolland, Romain Longman's n.d. 2:68
Living Thoughts of Tolstoi, The Zweig, Stefan Longman's n.d. 2:68
Long Journey, The Jensen, Johannes V. Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:50
Lord Is a Man of War, The Donath, Stanley F. Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:50
Lot's Wife Ley-Piscator, Maria Bobbs-Merrill n.d. 1:10
Lovers, The Winsor, Kathleen Appleton-Century-Crofts n.d. 1:6
Mad Grandeur Gogarty, Oliver St. John Lippincott 1941 2:64
Madame Curie Curie, Eve The Book-of-the-Month Club 1943-46 1:11
Madame Dorothea Undset, Sigrid Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 1:52
Madchen und Frauen Zweig, Arnold Kiepenheuer n.d. 1:44
Malenski auf der Tour Roeld, Otto Erich Reiss Verlag n.d. 3:86
Mandelbaum Gate, The Spark, Muriel Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:60
Manhattan Transfer Dos Passos, John Houghton Mifflin Co. 1943 1:42
Manner von St. Kilda, Die Kuhnert, A. Artur Philipp Reclam Verlag n.d. 3:84
Maquisard Guerard, Albert J. Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:50
Marriage of Elizabeth Whitaker, The Hichens, Jacobine Little Brown and Co. 1953 2:67
Marriage of Elizabeth Whitaker, The Hichens, Jacobine Duell, Sloane and Pearce -- Little Brown n.d. 1:19
Matriarch Chronicles, The Stern, G.B. Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:51
Maxim Litvinoff Nunberg, R.M. L.B. Fisher n.d. 1:24
Meine Mutter Tcheng, Cheng Kiepenheuer n.d. 1:44
Melville Goodwin, USA Marquand, John P. Little Brown and Co. 1951 2:66
Memoirs and Correspondence, The Lawrence, Frieda Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:56
Memory of Love Breuer, Bessie Simon and Schuster Inc. 1934 3:93
Men of Art Craven, Thomas Simon and Schuster Inc. 1935 3:94
Mensch auf der Flucht, Der Stueuermann, Carl S. Fisher Verlag, Berlin n.d. 1:27
Mental Hospital, The Schwartz, Morris and Stanton, Alfred H. Basic Books n.d. 1:8
Mermaid Tavern Cronyn, George W. Knight Publications 1936 1:48
Mind of the South, The Cash, W.J. Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:59
Miracle in Brittany Jordan, Mildred Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:55
Miracle in Brittany Jordan, Mildred Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:63
Miracle in the Rain Hecht, Ben Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:51
Mist in the Tagus Hopkinson, Tom Little Brown and Co. 1946 2:65
Moons Ride Over, The Zuckmayer, Carl Viking Press Inc. 1936 3:101
Moskau in Flammen Lukasch, Iwan Dietrich Reimer Verlag n.d. 3:85
Most Private Intrigue, A Rosten, Leo Atheneum n.d. 1:3
Mother and Son Hatano, Isoko and Ichiro Houghton Mifflin Co. 1962 1:42
Mother and Son Freyre, Gilberto Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:60
Mrs. Biest Pfeieft Smith, Helen Zenna S. Fisher Verlag, Berlin n.d. 1:27
Mrs. Panopoulis Godden, Jon Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:58
Mud on the Stars Huie, William Bradford L.B. Fisher n.d. 1:24
Murder for the Millions Owen, Frank (ed.) Frederick Fell n.d. 1:23
Murder With Pictures Coxe, George Harmon Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:52
My Austria Schuschnigg, Kurt Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:51
My Heart for Hostage Hillyer, Robert Random House 1942 2:80
My Life and History Szeps, Berta Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:52
My Old World Dimnet, Ernest Simon and Schuster Inc. 1934 3:93
Narziss and Goldmund Hesse, Hermann Harper 1965 1:35
New England Reader, A Brooks, Van Wyck (ed.) Atheneum n.d. 1:3
New Frontiers of the Mind Rhine, J.B. Farrar and Rhinehart n.d. 1:22
New Inquisition, The Heiden, Konrad Alliance n.d. 1:2
New Spirit, The Ellis, Havelock National House Library 1935 2:73
Newspaper Days 1899-1906 Mencken, H.L. Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:50
Night Cry Stuart, William L. Dial Press n.d. 1:17
Night of the Poor Prokosch, Frederic Harper 1939 1:35
Night of the Poor Prokosch, Frederic Harper 1939 1:36
Night of Time, The Fulop-Miller, Rene Bobbs-Merrill n.d. 1:10
Nightmare of the Dark Silberstang, Edwin Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:60
Nine Days to Mukalla Prokosch, Frederic Viking Press Inc. 1952 3:102
No Hero--This Deeping, Warwick Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:52
North of Grand Central Marquand, John P. Little Brown and Co. 1956 2:67
Nymph and the Lamp, The Raddall, Thomas H. Little Brown and Co. 1950 2:66
Obedience to the Moon Gibbs, A. Hamilton Little Brown and Co. 1955 2:67
Of Mice and Men Steinbeck, John Covici-Friede 1937 1:15
Offshore Light, The Naylor, Eliot Little Brown and Co. 1953 2:67
Old Calabria Douglas, Norman Oxford University Press 1938 2:74
Old Heart Goes A-Journeying, An Fallada, Hans Simon and Schuster Inc. 1936 3:94
On Borrowed Time Watkin, Lawrence Edward Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:52
Once a Greek… Duerrenmatt, Friedrich Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:59
Oppenheim Secret Service Omnibus, The Oppenheim, E. Phillips Little Brown and Co. 1946 2:65
Ordeal of Gilbert Pinfold, The Waugh, Evelyn Little Brown and Co. 1957 2:67
Origins and History of Consciousness, The Neumann, Erich Harper 1961 1:35
Other Side of the Summer, The Huguenin, Jean-Rene George Braziller n.d. 1:12
Out of the Night Valtin, Jan Alliance n.d. 1:2
Paradies Amerika Kisch, Egon Erwin Erich Reiss Verlag n.d. 3:86
Paris Stone, Sasha Klinkhardt & Biermann Verlag n.d. 1:47
Paris Uber Mir Mendelssohn, Peter Philipp Reclam Verlag n.d. 3:84
Passage to India, A Forster, E.M. Penguin 1945 2:76
Patchwork Time, The Gibbons, Robert Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 1:49
People With the Dogs, The Stead, Christina Little Brown and Co. 1951 2:66
Pflasterkasten, Die Frey, A.M. Kiepenheuer n.d. 1:46
Pflichten der Juden und von den Pflichten des Staates, Von den Brunner, Constantine Kiepenheuer n.d. 1:44
Philosopher's Holiday Edman, Irwin Viking Press Inc. 1938 3:101
Player's Handbook of Short Scenes, A Selden, Samuel Holiday House 1960 1:30
Pledge, The Duerrenmatt, Friedrich Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:60
Point of No Return Marquand, John P. Little Brown and Co. 1948 2:66
Popular History of the World, A Wood, Clement Grosset & Dunlap n.d. 1:30
Portable Dante, The Viking Press Inc. 1954 3:103
Portable Greek Reader, The Auden, W.H., ed. Viking Press Inc. 1954 3:103
Portable Plato, The Buchanan, Scott, ed. Viking Press Inc. 1955 3:103
Portrait in Brownstone Auchincloss, Louis Houghton Mifflin Co. n.d. 1:42
Possess Me Not Nichols, Fan Frederick Fell n.d. 1:23
Prince of Thieves, The Lynx, J.J. Atheneum n.d. 1:3
Prisoners of Hope Brooks, Howard L. L.B. Fisher n.d. 1:24
Promise, The Gram, Mildred Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 1:49
Quartet Ludwig, Emil Alliance n.d. 1:2
Quartett zu dritt Reimann, Hans Kiepenheuer n.d. 1:45
Queen Pedauque, The France, Anatole National House Library n.d. 2:73
Quest, The Langgasser, Elisabeth Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:54
Radetzky Marsch Roth, Joseph Kiepenheuer n.d. 1:44
Radium Brunngraber, Rudolf Random House 1937 2:80
Raft, The Trumbull, Robert Holt 1942 1:41
Rancho of the Little Loves, The Nathan, Robert Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:56
Rancho of the Little Loves, The Nathan, Robert Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:63
Receive the Gale Wickes, Frances G. Appleton n.d. 1:4
Red and the Black, The Stendhal Random House 1957 3:82
Red Neck Coleman, McAlister and Raushenbush, Stephen Smith and Haas 1936 3:95
Reise ins Innere, Die Heuser, Kurt S. Fisher Verlag, Berlin n.d. 1:26
Reise nach Genf, Die Beer, Max S. Fisher Verlag n.d. 1:25
Report on Bruno Breitbach, Joseph Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:60
Report on Bruno Breitbach, Joseph Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:61
Requiem for Idols Lofts, Norah Knopf, Alfred A. 1938 2:52
Requiem for Idols Lofts, Norah Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 1:49
Requiem for Idols Lofts, Norah Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:52
Rest They Need, The Lyons, Herbert Dial Press n.d. 1:17
Rettung, Die Conrad, Joseph S. Fisher Verlag, Berlin n.d. 1:26
Riders in the Chariot White, Patrick Viking Press Inc. 1961 3:102
Riley McCullough Jonas, Carl Little Brown and Co. 1954 2:67
River Journey, The Nathan, Robert Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 1:49
Robinson Crusoe Defoe, Daniel National House Library n.d. 2:73
Rockets Through Space Cleator, P.E. Simon and Schuster Inc. 1935 3:94
Romance of Tea, The Ukers, William H. Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:52
Romeo im Fegefeuer Seidl, Walter Erich Reiss Verlag n.d. 3:86
Room With a View, A Forster, E.M. Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:59
Roosevelt and Home Rollins, Alfred B. Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:59
Roots of Scientific Thought Noland, Aaron and Wiener, Philip P. (eds.) Basic Books n.d. 1:8
Roots of the Tree, The Todd, Helen Houghton Mifflin Co. 1944 1:42
Rothschilds, The Morton, Frederic Atheneum n.d. 1:3
Salammbo Flaubert, Gustave National House Library n.d. 2:73
Salvatia Russell, Elizabeth Transmare Verlag n.d. 3:89
San Luca, The Ofaire, Cilette Simon and Schuster Inc. 1934 3:93
Sands of Karakorum, The Ullman, James Ramsey Lippincott 1953 2:64
Schacht, Hitler's Magician Muhlen, Norbert Alliance n.d. 1:2
Schatten Affair, The Morton, Frederic Atheneum n.d. 1:3
Schreib das auf, Kisch! Erich Reiss Verlag n.d. 3:87
Schwierige Tod, Der Crevel, Rene S. Fisher Verlag, Berlin n.d. 1:26
Schwindel Karlweis, Marta S. Fisher Verlag, Berlin n.d. 1:27
See How They Run Mankiewicz, Don M. Knopf, Alfred A. 1951 2:55
Selections from the Writings of Thomas Paine Paine, Thomas National House Library n.d. 2:73
Sense of Beauty, The Santayana, George Random House 1955 3:82
Seven Arms, The Strong, L.A.G. Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:53
Seven Islands, The Godden, Jon Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:54
Seven Islands, The Godden, Jon Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:63
Seven Who Fled Prokosch, Frederic Harper 1937 1:36
Shadow Without Light Richards, S.L.M. Dial Press n.d. 1:17
Shadowed Valley, The Schachtel, Hyman Judah Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:58
Shepherds of the Night Amado, Jorge Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:59
Shining Scabbard Hutchinson, R.C. Farrar and Rhinehart n.d. 1:22
Sigmund Freud: Four Century Addresses Jones, Ernest Basic Books n.d. 1:8
Silberne Windfahne, Die Kluge, Kurt Engelhorn n.d. 1:21
Silver Bacchanal, The Fulop-Miller, Rene Atheneum n.d. 1:3
Sincerely, Willis Wayde Marquand, John P. Little Brown and Co. 1954 2:67
Single Pebble, A Hersey, John Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:53
Six of Them Neumann, Alfred MacMillan 1945 2:70
Sketch of My Life, A Mann, Thomas Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:56
Skies of Europe Prokosch, Frederic Harper 1941 1:36
Slanting Light, A Charles, Gerda Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:56
Snare of the Fowler, The Bullett, Gerald Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:51
Snow Goose, The Gallico, Paul Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:51
So Love Returns Nathan, Robert Pyramid Books 1962 2:79
So sind wir! Matzke, Frank Philipp Reclam Verlag n.d. 3:84
Sons and Fathers Hindus, Maurice Doubleday, Doran & Co. n.d. 1:18
Sound of an American, The Ormsbee, David Dutton n.d. 1:20
Spanish Gardener, The Cronin, A.J. Little Brown and Co. 1950 2:66
Stadt Anatol, Die Kellermann, Berhard S. Fisher Verlag n.d. 1:27
Standarte, Die Lernet-Holenia, Alexander S. Fisher Verlag n.d. 1:27
Stepchildren of France Odic, Charles Roy Publishers 1945 3:90
Stories of Three Decades Mann, Thomas Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:52
Story of a Novel, The Mann, Thomas Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:56
Story of Civilization, The Durant, Will Simon and Schuster Inc. 1935 3:93
Strange and Fantastic Stories Margolies, Joseph A., ed. Whittlesey House 1946 3:104
Stravinsky Stravinsky, Igor Simon and Schuster Inc. 1935 3:94
Strich drunter Graves, Robert Transmare Verlag n.d. 3:89
Swastika Schisgall, Oscar Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:50
Take It Easy Pitkin, Walter B. Simon and Schuster Inc. n.d. 3:93
Tale For Midnight, A Prokosch, Frederic Little Brown and Co. 1955 2:67
Tale For Midnight, A Prokosch, Frederic Little Brown and Co. 1955 2:67
Tale of Two Cities, A Dickens, Charles National House Library n.d. 2:73
Tales Kipling, Rudyard National House Library n.d. 2:73
Tales Tolstoy, Leo National House Library n.d. 2:73
Taw Jameson Martenet, May Davies Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:54
That Day Alone van Paassen, Pierre Dial Press 1941 1:17
These Are the Virgin Islands Cochran, Hamilton Prentice Hall n.d. 2:78
They Shall Inherit the Earth Callaghan, Morley Random House 1935 2:80
Thing of Beauty, A Cronin, A.J. Little Brown and Co. 1956 2:67
Things That Are Caesar's, The Katz, Milton Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:56
Thirty Years Marquand, John P. Little Brown and Co. 1954 2:67
Thirty-First Floor, The Wahloo, Peter Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:56
This Gun For Hire Greene, Graham Doubleday, Doran & Co. n.d. 1:18
Thomas Mann Reader, The Angell, Joseph Warner Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:54
Though Young Barret, Leighton Random House 1938 2:80
Thunder in the Heart Weldon, John Lee Random House 1953 3:82
Thy Tears Might Cease Farrell, Michael Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:61
Time of the Gringo, The Arnold, Elliott Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:54
Time to Love and a Time to Die, A Remarque, Erich Maria Harcourt, Brace and Co. 1954 1:34
Time: The Present Slesinger, Tess Simon and Schuster Inc. 1935 3:93
Torchlight to Valhalla Wilhelm, Gale Random House 1938 2:80
Train in the Meadow, The Nathan, Robert Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:53
Transposed Heads, The Mann, Thomas Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:51
Traum und Schicksal Schnitzler, Arthur S. Fisher Verlag n.d. 1:25
Traum vom grossen Gluck, Der Huelsenbeck, Richard S. Fisher Verlag, Berlin n.d. 1:27
Treasury of Doctor Stories, A Fabricant, Noah D. and Werner Heinz Frederick Fell n.d. 1:23
Treatise on the Gods Mencken, H.L. Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:59
Tree of Man, The White, Patrick Viking Press Inc. 1955 3:102
Treibgut Green, Julien Kiepenheuer n.d. 1:46
Twilight on the Danube Weiskopf, F.C. Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:50
Two Under the Indian Sun Godden, Jon and Rumer Viking Press Inc. 1966 3:102
Two Under the Indian Sun Godden, Jon and Rumer Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:61
Two Worlds of Johnny Truro, The Sklar, George Little Brown and Co. 1946 2:65
Ultimate Frog, The Dickinson, Roy Vanguard 1939 3:100
Under the Eye of the Storm Hersey, John Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:58
Under the Open Sky Nexo, Martin Andersen Vanguard 1936 3:100
Unfinished Journey Jones, Jack Oxford University Press 1937 2:74
Union Now Streit, Clarence K. Harper 1941 1:35
Union Now With Britain Streit, Clarence K. Harper 1941 1:35
Union Now With Britain Streit, Clarence K. Harper 1941 1:36
Unknown Quantity, The Broch, Herman Viking Press Inc. 1935 3:101
Unleashed Will, The Clark, Christopher Little Brown and Co. 1946 2:65
Untat, Die Sochaczener Kiepenheuer n.d. 1:44
Until I Find Pinchon, Edgcumb Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:52
Verdammten, Die Thiess, Frank Kiepenheuer n.d. 1:46
Verdammtes Gold O'Flaherty, Liam S. Fisher Verlag n.d. 1:25
Verdi, The Man in His Letters Werfel, Franz L.B. Fisher n.d. 1:24
Very Small Remnant, A Straight, Michael Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:59
Vierundzwanzig Stunden Bromfield, Louis Erich Reiss Verlag n.d. 3:87
Violent Season, The Goulet, Robert George Braziller n.d. 1:12
Visitor, the Randau, Carl and Zugsmith, Leane Random House 1943 2:80
Voice of the Turtle, The van Druten, John Random House 1944 2:80
Wanglung der Susanne Dasseldorf, Die Breitbach, Josef Kiepenheuer n.d. 1:46
War Below Zero: The Battle for Greenland Balchen, Bernt; Ford, Corey and Lafarge Oliver Houghton Mifflin Co. 1944 1:42
War Tomorrow: Will We Keep Out? Foreign Policy Association n.d. 1:28
Waters of Kronos, The Richter, Conrad Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:53
Weans, The Nathan, Robert Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:56
Weans, The Nathan, Robert Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:63
Weihnachts Katalog Klinkhardt & Biermann Verlag n.d. 1:47
Welt der Herzen, Die Mann, Heinrich Kiepenheuer n.d. 1:44
While Still We Live MacInnes, Helen Little Brown and Co. 1943 2:65
Who Walk Alone Burgess, Perry Holt 1940 1:41
Wiedersehn mit Amerika Holitscher, Arthur S. Fisher Verlag n.d. 1:25
Willie Mae Kytle, Elizabeth Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:56
Willie Mae Kytle, Elizabeth Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:63
Winter Orchard Johnson, Josephine Simon and Schuster Inc. 1935 3:94
Winter's Tale, A Godden, Jon Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:56
Winter's Tales Dinesen, Isak Random House 1942 2:80
Winter's Tales Dinesen, Isak Random House 1942 3:83
Without Seeing the Dawn Javellana, Stevan Little Brown and Co. 1946 2:65
World in Trance Schwarzschild, Leopold L.B. Fisher n.d. 1:24
World My Wilderness, The Macaulay, Rose Little Brown and Co. 1950 2:66
World of Love, A Bowe, Elizabeth Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:54
Wort der Manner, Das London, Jack Universitas, Berlin n.d. 3:99
Young and the Immortal, The Currier, Isabel Knopf, Alfred A. n.d. 2:5
- Series I. ARTWORK BY GEORGE SALTER, 1934-1967
  - Book designs (covers, book jackets, endpapers), [See Box 4: Folder 143a for lists of Salter book jackets arranged by author, by title, by publisher, and by date]
    - Listing 1934-1967: holograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Alliance (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Atheneum (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Appleton (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Appleton-Century (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Appleton-Century-Crofts (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Atlas Magazine (1961-1962) (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Basic Books (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Bibliographisches Institut (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Bobbs-Merill (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - The Book-of-the-Month-Club (1943-1946, n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - George Braziller (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Columbia University Press (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Columbia University Press (1965, n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Covici-Friede (1937) (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Crowell publishers (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Dial Press (1941, n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Doubleday, Doran & Company (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Duell, Sloane and Pearce-Little Brown (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Dutton (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Engelhorn, J. (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Farrar and Rhinehart (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Fell, Frederick (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Fisher, L.B. (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Fisher, S. Verlag (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Fisher, S. Verlag (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Fisher, S. Verlag (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Foreign Policy Association (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Funk & Wagnalls (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Grosset & Dunlap (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Gebrüder Enoch (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Grote, G. Verlag (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Grote, G. Verlag, illustrations (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Harcourt, Brace (1954-1961) (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Harper (1937-1965) (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Harper, endpapers (1937-1942, n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Harpers (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Hillman-Curl (1939) (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Hillman-Curl, endpaper (1939) (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Holiday House (1960) (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Holt (1940-1942) (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Houghton Mifflin Company (1943-1967) (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Huntington Press (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Kiepenheuer, Gustav, Verlag (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Kiepenheuer, Gustav, Verlag (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Kiepenheuer, Gustav, Verlag (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Klinkhardt & Biermann Verlag (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Knight Publications (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Knopf, Alfred A. (n.d.) (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Knopf, Alfred A. (n.d.) (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Knopf, Alfred A. (Includes orig. artwork of Apple in the Attic) 1964 (Box 2, Folder 51)
      [see also Oversize, Box:5, Folder:152]
    - Knopf, Alfred A. (n.d.) (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Knopf, Alfred A. (n.d.) (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Knopf, Alfred A. (n.d.) (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Knopf, Alfred A (n.d.) (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Knopf, Alfred A. (n.d.) (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Knopf, Alfred A. (n.d.) (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Knopf, Alfred A. (n.d.) (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Knopf, Alfred A. (n.d.) (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Knopf, Alfred A (n.d.) (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Knopf, Alfred A. (n.d.) (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Knopf, Alfred A., endpapers (n.d.) (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Knopf, Alfred A., (n.d.) (Box 2, Folder 63)
      [see also Oversize, Box:5, Folder:146]
    - Lippincott (J.B.) Company (1941-1953, n.d.) (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Little Brown and Company (1936-1946, n.d.) (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Little Brown and Company (1947-1951, n.d.) (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Little Brown and Company (1953-1957,n.d.) (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Longman's, (Living Thoughts Lib.) (1939-1940, n.d.) (Box 2, Folder 68)
      [see also Oversize, Box:5, Folder:147]
    - McDowell, Obolensky (1957) (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Macmillan Publishing Comp. (1945-1947) (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Messner (1964) (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Methuen Publishing Ltd. (1937) (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - National Home Library (n.d.) (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Oxford University Press (1937-1938, n.d.) (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Pantheon (1966) (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Penguin Books (1945) (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Phönix-Verlag, Carl Siwinna (n.d.) (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Prentice Hall Inc. (n.d.) (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Pyramid Books (1962) (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Random House (1935-1944, n.d.) (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Random House (1945-1953, n.d.) (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Random House (1953-1957) (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Random House, endpapers (1942-1948) (Box 3, Folder 83)
      [see also Oversize, Box:5, Folder:148]
    - Verlag Philipp Reclam (n.d.) (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Dietrich Reimer Verlag (n.d.) (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Eric Reiss Verlag (n.d.) (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Eric Reiss Verlag (n.d.) (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Verlag E.A. Seemann (n.d.) (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Transmare Verlag (n.d.) (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - Roy Publishers (1943-1945, n.d.) (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Schmiede Verlag (n.d.) (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Scribners and Company (1943) (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Simon and Schuster Inc. (1934-1936, n.d.) (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Simon and Schuster (1935-1937) (Box 3, Folder 94)
      [see also Oversize, Box:5, Folder:149]
    - Smith and Haas (1935-1936, n.d.) (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Szolsnay, Paul Verlag (n.d.) (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Stokes, Friedrich A. (1935) (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - Time Inc. (1964) (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Universitas, Berlin (n.d.) (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Venguard (1936-1939, n.d.) (Box 3, Folder 100)